fun2gag.com 2013-11-26

# Privacy Policy

Fun2gag respects the privacy concerns of the users of its Internet Sites (“Sites”), and has created this privacy statement to explain what information we gather from your visit to our Sites, and how such information may be used.

Use of Information

As a general policy, no personally identifiable information, such as your name or address, is automatically collected from your visit to fun2gag. However, certain non-personal information is recorded by the standard operation of fun2gag’s Internet servers. Information such as the type of browser being used, its operating system, and your IP address is gathered in order to enhance your online experience. For example, it may be used to tailor content and advertising to your interests.

In special cases, fun2gag may disclose user information when there is reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to, or interference (either intentionally or unintentionally) with, fun2gag’s rights or property, other fun2gag web site users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities.

Security  
Security for all personally identifiable information is extremely important to us. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. While we strive to protect your personal information, fun2gag cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online forms, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.

Use of Cookies

Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual’s computer hard drive for record keeping purposes. Cookies are used to track visits to our Sites and to personalize the Sites for new and current subscribers. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies; however, you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. (Note: you will need to consult the help area of your browser application for instructions.) If you choose to disable your cookies setting or refuse to accept a cookie, some parts of fun2gag’s web sites may not function properly.

Use of IP Addresses

An IP address is a number that’s automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet provider whenever you surf the Web. When you request pages from fun2gag Sites, our servers log your IP address. Fun2gag collects IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, to report aggregate information to our advertisers, and to audit the use of our Site. We may use your IP addresses in cooperation with your Internet provider to identify you if we deem it necessary to enforce compliance with our Terms of Use or to protect our service, Sites, customers, or others.

Links to Other Sites

Fun2gag is not responsible for the content or practices of third party websites that may be linked to our Sites. Our Sites may link to websites operated by other companies; we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such websites. Visitors to these web sites should refer to each web site’s respective privacy policies and practices.

Third Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to our sites, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, visit the Network Advertising Initiative or Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our websites. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

Contact Us

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of our Sites, or your dealings with our Sites, you can email us

Information provided by you via general email inquiries to fun2gag such as your email address is used only to respond to your inquiries in the ordinary course of business, and is never shared with third parties.

Acceptance of These Terms

By using fun2gag and its Sites, you signify your acceptance of the fun2gag Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Sites. Fun2gag reserves the right to modify, alter or otherwise update this policy at any time. We encourage visitors to review this policy from time to time. Your continued use of the fun2gag Sites following the posting of changes to these terms indicates your acceptance of these changes

The Ultimate Destination For Free Download, Sharing And Viewing Of The Funniest Pictures, Fails, IPhone Autocorrects, Wallpapers, Movies Scenes, Troll Comics Online, Funny Iphone Texts ,Epic Pictures, Meme Comics, Facebook Status Fails, Funny Animal Photos, Rage Comics, Lol Photos, Tv Series Funny Photos, Photoshop Fails, Boyfriend – Girlfriend Texts And Much More Funny Stuffs. Kill Your Boredom And Have A Fun Time At Fun2gag. Updated Daily. Do Recommend It To Your Friends.
